let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Oxidation is a process which involves?",
    answer: "addition of oxygen",
    options: [
      "removal of oxygen",
      "removal of hydrogen",
      "addition of hydrogen",
      "addition of oxygen"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is an endothermic process? ",
    answer: "Sublimation of dry ice",
    options: [
      " Dilution of sulphuric acid",
      "Sublimation of dry ice",
      "Condensation of water vapours",
      "Respiration in human beings"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: ". What type of chemical reactions take place when electricity is passed through water?",
    answer: "Decomposition",
    options: [
      "Decomposition",
      "Combination",
      "Double displacement",
      " Displacement"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Which of the following gases can be used for storage?",
    answer: " Helium or Nitrogen",
    options: [
      " Helium or Nitrogen",

      " Nitrogen or Oxygen",
      
      " Carbon dioxide or Oxygen",
      
      "Carbon dioxide or Helium"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following reactions will not take place ?",
    answer: "Zn + MgSO4 → ZnSO4 + Mg",
    options: [
      "Zn + CuSO4 → ZnSO3 + Cu",
      "Zn + MgSO4 → ZnSO4 + Mg",
      " 2KBr + Cl2 → KCl + Br2",
      " Mg + FeSO4 → MgSO4 + Fe"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following involves combination of two elements ?",
    answer: "N2(g) + 3H2(g) → 2NH3(g)",
    options: [
      "N2(g) + 3H2(g) → 2NH3(g)",
      " CaO(s) + CO2(g) → CaCO3(g)",
      "2SO2(g) + O2(g) → 2SO3f(g)",
      "NH3(g) + HCl(g) → NH4Cl(s)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The brown gas evolved on heating of copper nitrate is",
    answer: "NO2",
    options: [
      " O2",
      "N2",
      "NO2",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following mirror is used by a dentist to examine a small cavity?",
    answer: "Concave mirror",
    options: [
      "Convex mirror",
      " Plane mirror",
      "Concave mirror",
      "Combination of convex and concave mirror"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "As light travels from a rarer to a denser medium it will have",
    answer: " both (b) and (c)",
    options: [
      "increased velocity",
      "decreased velocity",
      "decreased wavelength",
      " both (b) and (c)"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 10,
    question: "The angle of incidence i and refraction r are equal in a transparent slab when the value of i is",
    answer: "0°",
    options: [
      "0°",
      "45°",
      "90°",
      "depend on the material of the slab"
    ]
  }
  
];
